[{"answer": "Well, it's a little too early. I'd say Thursday would be good. I'll know by then. Is that all right", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'll come by", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'll come by", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Seven o'clock", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm always here for you", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I am", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm positive", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You're a little confused", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, we're lookin' for my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I care about you, a", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Understand?  I'm sorry", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I'm not crying.", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Maybe you shouldn't drink so much", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It's all right. That part of your life is over with. Right", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You called my friend a faggot? You tell him to go fuck himself", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Is that what you did", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, I did", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I did", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "The action is in the front, not in the back. Bring 'em up front", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Listen to me very carefully. There are three ways of doing things around here. The right way, the wrong way, and the way I do it. You understand", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "All right, I will, I will", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I do understand that. I'll get right on it. And thank you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Forget it. You can't even set foot in the parking lot. That's how serious it is", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "In so many words, yes", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "But how much cash could I bury in my closet, right", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, listen, I understand that there's always a risk... you know, I might have to take a loss somewhere", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Made a messenger out of you too, huh", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "He does it. He does it to everybody. Enjoy your dinner", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " You walk past me", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Hey, my friend.", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "How are you? Nice to meet you", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend.", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " And this is my friend", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " This is my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "A couple of guys, I owe them. So, that's what I did. I gave 'em the money.  That's what I did", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No, no? You didn't", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Don't fuck with me, my friend! Don't make a fuck out of me! You want to embarrass me and make a fool out of me?!  You didn't gamble?! Tell me you gambled the fuckin' money, I'll give you the fuckin' money to put the fuckin' heat on! Did you gamble?! Huh?", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Fuckin' kids at home!  Here.  Get the fuck out of here", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yeah, thanks", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " How many of these you gonna eat, huh", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Two", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Oh, God! Give me the fuckin' name", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Charlie M", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "C", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " Charlie M", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Charlie M? You make me pop your fuckin' eye out of your head to protect that piece of shit? Charlie M? You dumb motherfucker", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Kill you,  You motherfucker you!  my friend, do him a fuckin' favor", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Shoot, it's gotta be in the millions, maybe more", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Well, it happened so quick. Three guys won. I didn't have a chance to call you", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yes, there is. An infallible way! They won", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Hey... my friend, you're pissin' me off. Now, you're insulting my intelligence. What do you think, I'm a fuckin' idiot? You know goddamn well somebody had to get into those machines and set those fuckin' reels", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "What are you talkin' ", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You're askin' me for twent", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "What does that mean? No, I know that look. What does that mean", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You got money. That's a", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, there you go. But what does that tell ya? A million dollars in jewelry. Does that tell you the guy is crazy about you, or what", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I know what you mean", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " Isn't it bad enough you're drinkin' too much, you're takin' all my pills too", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Look", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Yes, you do. It's very discreet. There's no names in the papers. You don't have to worry about any of that stuff", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " Yes, I", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "That's all you care about.  You don't care about me at all", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No, you don't", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "What the hell have you been doin' out there", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Your cumma? What are you doin' with your cumma", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "What expenses", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "You gotta go back out there", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Why are you doing this to me", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I'm not wrong", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "I'm not wrong", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "No, I am not wrong", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Why, of course, he really said that. It's right here. Has that man even filed for his license yet", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Well, without gettin' your shorts in a knot, would you do that? And kinda check closely, 'cause we may have to kick a kike's ass out of town.  Thank you", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " You mean, quiet like thi", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Yeah, that's out of context. Okay", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Every time you're on television I get mentioned. That looks bad. That looks bad", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "What happened to me? What happened to you", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "I lost control", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "You lost your control", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Yes, you lost your control", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Mom, I'm sorry, they're beatin' me left and right.  Ma, I'm sorry. I'm all upset", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "You know", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": " I know, but that's enough", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "I know it, I know it", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "I know it, I know it", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Take it easy, though", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Adjourned! What do you mean, adjourned", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "Mr. Chairman..", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "Was I at that dinner? Just tell me", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "Was I at that dinner", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "You were wandering around", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "You were wandering around", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "Was I at that dinner", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "Was I at that dinner", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "You were wandering around", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "You were wandering around", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "Was I at that dinner", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "Was I at that dinner", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "You were wandering around", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "You were in the ", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": "Was I at that dinner", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": "I was in the building", "qsentId": 106}, {"answer": "What's he doin'? He knows all those guys he yelled at are friends of ours. What's the matter with him, making all this mess", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 109, "question": "However he runs things, it's gotta be quiet. Let him hide upstairs in the office. Say he's the janitor, I don't give a shit. But, please, whatever job he takes, make sure it's something quiet", "qsentId": 108}, {"answer": "...Well, I've got a large family", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 111, "question": " Uh, I'm very proud to say that we have eight children", "qsentId": 110}, {"answer": "Sue me, you Jew fuck", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 113, "question": "What? Get out of here? I got a marker comin'", "qsentId": 112}, {"answer": " 702 472 1862", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 115, "question": " Right away", "qsentId": 114}, {"answer": "M", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 117, "question": " I'll call you right back", "qsentId": 116}, {"answer": "Hey... you got a minute? Hey. He's got two million in the box, am I right?  Okay, you let him keep your jewels. We take the cash and the only other thing he cares about.  Huh?  Her majesty. We go to that place. You dye your hair, get some p", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 119, "question": "We're not gonna go see any fuckin' elephants, okay", "qsentId": 118}, {"answer": " So, he knows where you are. That means he's sending some guys over here probably right now", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 121, "question": " That's", "qsentId": 120}, {"answer": "It's this bullshit. It's just bullshit right here. This is the fuckin' problem, you know", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 123, "question": "You're done yakkin', okay? You're done yakkin' now", "qsentId": 122}, {"answer": "You're done yakkin', okay? You're done yakkin' now", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 125, "question": " 'Go! Go! Go!", "qsentId": 124}, {"answer": "You're not gonna drive. Don't even think you're gonna drive", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 127, "question": " No, I'm not gonna drive with some crazy", "qsentId": 126}, {"answer": "No, I'm gonna drive", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 129, "question": " You're driving me nuts", "qsentId": 128}, {"answer": " How serious", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 131, "question": " It's under..", "qsentId": 130}, {"answer": " Twent", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 133, "question": "Twent", "qsentId": 132}, {"answer": "I bought him a watch too", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 135, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 134}, {"answer": " Would you knock it off, my friend", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 137, "question": "There's nothin' to figure out. I'm home... we're workin' it out", "qsentId": 136}, {"answer": "Tell me what you were gonna say. Go ahead", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 139, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 138}, {"answer": "He's so fuckin' lucky. I could have buried him. I could have gone to that place and taken the baby. And then he'd've tracked me down and he'd've killed me", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 141, "question": " I didn't.  I didn't. I mean, I did, but then I did exactly what you told me to do, and I came right back", "qsentId": 140}, {"answer": "No, he wouldn't. I would have.  And he'd've been right, too. I mean, seriously.  Well, there's one thing you don't do. You don't take a guy's kid and then take off", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 143, "question": "You did. You're right", "qsentId": 142}, {"answer": "You did. I like that. I like that. That's what I like about you. You did the right thing", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 145, "question": "Yes, you did", "qsentId": 144}, {"answer": "Hi. You didn't answer your beeper", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 147, "question": "You threw it away", "qsentId": 146}, {"answer": "To the that place", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 149, "question": "I had a... salad", "qsentId": 148}, {"answer": " What'd you have", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 151, "question": "What did my friend have", "qsentId": 150}, {"answer": "I had a... salad", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 153, "question": " She had the same", "qsentId": 152}, {"answer": " Okay. I want you to call my friend and I want you to tell her to tell you what she had for lunch, and I'm gonna listen in on the other line", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 155, "question": "You know why I want to do it. Just do it", "qsentId": 154}, {"answer": "All right... I didn't have lunch with my friend", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 157, "question": " I was with somebody", "qsentId": 156}, {"answer": " Who were you with", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 159, "question": "I know you were with somebody. Who was it?  I just hope it's not someone who I think it might be.  I just hope it's not them", "qsentId": 158}, {"answer": "Of course, Remo", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 161, "question": "I always tell you the truth, Remo", "qsentId": 160}, {"answer": "Yeah, what's to stop him", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 163, "question": "I don't trust him anymore. But they'd never okay anything, you know", "qsentId": 162}, {"answer": "my friend, any calls for me, just give 'em to Mr my friend. I'll be right back", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 165, "question": "I'm going home for a few seconds. I'll be right back", "qsentId": 164}, {"answer": "I'll sign anything you want me to sign, okay", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 167, "question": "I just want the key to my jewelry, and I want you to let me go", "qsentId": 166}, {"answer": "You want your jewelry", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 169, "question": "And what? And let you disgrace me, you fuckin' pig? And let you disgrace me?  Get up. Get up and be a mother. Get in the car and go to the house..", "qsentId": 168}, {"answer": "I told you this was fuckin' dangerous. Remember I said, 'Ginger, this is a dangerous situation. Be very careful.' You fuckin' yessed me to death", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 171, "question": "I'm not gonna kill him. Shut the fuck up. What, do you know what you're talkin' about? I'm not killing any", "qsentId": 170}, {"answer": "I am not", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 173, "question": "Don't you threaten me", "qsentId": 172}, {"answer": "He won't let me go in my house", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 175, "question": "Not gonna let me in", "qsentId": 174}, {"answer": "That's not a problem, that's not a ", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 177, "question": "my friend, would you go in with her", "qsentId": 176}, {"answer": " You've got to stop her", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 179, "question": " She's a fuckin' junkie. She's out of her fucking mind.  Do you under", "qsentId": 178}, {"answer": " My name is my friend, Special Agent, that place", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 181, "question": " Hey, h", "qsentId": 180}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Casino.txt", "asentId": 183, "question": "No, I won't calm down! He's my husband", "qsentId": 182}]